(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-15T23:28:17.300138",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
うーん
Mmm...
待ってよ
Wait...
あー
Ah!
ニコニコ？
Smiling?
あらあら
My, my...
はむっ
Chomp!
いやー
No!
眠たい
I'm sleepy...
チョコも眠たい
Choco is sleepy too...
チョコ
Choco...
待って待って待って待って
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
あ、いやー！
Ah, nooo!
ふぁーあ
(Yawns)
どっち？
Which one?
やだやだやだやだ！
No, no, no, no!
どうもホロライブ二期生、悪魔の保健医、癒月ちょこです
Hello! I'm Yuzuki Choco, Hololive's 2nd generation demon health representative!
お前何しおっちゃ！
What are you doing?!
うわー！
Whoa!
Thank you so much, thank you very much!
ほら、豚、登って、頑張って、豚
Look, pig, climb! Keep going, pig!
ほら、豚、こっちよこっち、どっち？
Look, pig, this way, this way. Which one?
はいはいはいはい
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
なんだろう
I wonder what it is...
何年やってると思ってるんですか、え？
How many years do you think I've been doing this, huh?
先生に向かってなんですかその言葉遣いは！
What is that way of speaking to your teacher?!
友達じゃないんですよ！いいですか？
We are not friends! Understood?
癒月ちょこ先生だからね！
I am Yuzuki Choco-sensei, you know!
あ、やばい、うわー！
Oh, no! Waaa!
美味しかったの？
Was it delicious?
あ、違う！だめ！あー！
Ah, no! Stop! Ah!
チョコしかおらん
There's only Choco...
また動いた！また動いた！
It moved again! It moved again!
いらっしゃいませ
Welcome!
どこ？二期生？二期生？
Where? 2nd gen? 2nd gen?
うわー
Wow!
おやすみなさい
Goodnight.
あーあ
Sigh...
うしっ
Alright!
はーあ、HP1、保健室のベッドでお昼寝したーい
Haa... HP 1, I want to take a nap on the nurse's office bed...
昼休み スルーされない 保健室は神聖なの
Lunch break, not ignored, the nurse's office is sacred.
サボってる？ 今日だけだよ 誰も来ない やる気出ない
Slacking off? Just for today. Nobody's coming, I have no motivation.
チョコチョコせんせーしょん
Choco-Choco Sensation!
このままじゃ私 ダメみたい
Like this, it seems I'm no good.
あー 起きなきゃ ふとん 宝物
Ah, must wake up, my futon is a treasure...
2回目のあくび おやすみなさい
Second yawn, good night!
ごめんなさい 少しだけ寝かせて 先生モードシャットダウン
I'm sorry, let me sleep just a bit, Teacher Mode Shutdown!
夢見る ふわふわ ずっとこうして 眠りたい
Dreaming softly, I want to keep sleeping like this forever...
ありがとう ぽかぽか 今日は受付 閉めるだけ
Thank you, so warm, today I'm just closing reception.
油断大敵ね
No letting guard down!
急に君が来るなんて
You suddenly coming like that...
ね、どこか悪いの？
Hey, is something wrong?
何かを期待しているのかな？
Are you expecting something, I wonder?
揺れる心 巡る感情 口づけ 甘い 処方箋
Swaying heart, revolving emotions, a kiss, sweet prescription...
癒されたい 甘えていたい 構ってよ チョコせんせーしょん
Want to be healed, want to be spoiled, pay attention to me, Choco Sensation!
君の視線 君の体温 分かっても恋は測れない
Your gaze, your body temperature, even knowing them, love cannot be measured.
元気なのに溜息しちゃう モヤモヤしたのは何の病？
Sighing even though I'm fine, what kind of illness is this haziness?
胸ドキドキするまで動けないから ときめき運んできて マイ・シューズ
Can't move until my heart goes thud-thud, so bring me excitement, my shoes!
昼休み また来たの？ 保健室は神聖なの
Lunch break, did you come again? The nurse's office is sacred.
サボってた？ 嘘だけど やっぱり君に居てほしい
Slacking off? That's a lie, but I really want you to be here.
明日は週末 お休み なんだよ 家飲み 最高！
Tomorrow is the weekend! Days off! What's up with that? Drinking at home is the best!
引きこもり 最高！ もちろん ノーメイク
Staying indoors is the best! Of course, no makeup!
パジャマのままだったら 拍手いきます
If you're still in pajamas, let's give a round of applause!
さあ 全てを見せて ちゃんと診てあげるから
Now, show me everything, because I'll examine you properly.
何を隠してるの？ 鼓動のスピードは聞こえてるよ
What are you hiding? I can hear the speed of your heartbeat!
見せて心 めくるカルテ 正常保てる？ 臨床
Show me your heart, flipping medical chart, can we keep it normal? Clinical trial...
愛されたい 頼られたい 構ってよ チョコせんせーしょん
Want to be loved, want to be relied on, pay attention to me, Choco Sensation!
君の重み 君の匂い 分かっても愛は測れない
Your weight, your scent, even knowing them, love cannot be measured.
大好きなのに溜息しちゃう やっぱりそれは恋の病？
Sighing even though I love you, is that really love sickness?
胸ドキドキするまで動けないから ときめき運んできて マイ・シューズ
Can't move until my heart goes thud-thud, so bring me excitement, my shoes!
間違いだらけの この世界だって
Even in this world full of mistakes,
揺らぐ心 巡る感情 ちょっぴり甘いセンセーション
Wavering heart, circulating feelings, a slightly sweet sensation.
癒されたい？ 甘えていたい？ 大・大・大のちょこせんせーしょん
Want to be healed? Want to be pampered? The big, big, big Choco Sensation!
君の視線 君の体温 わかっても恋は測れない
Your gaze, your warmth... Even if I understand them, love cannot be measured.
元気なのに溜め息しちゃう もしかしてもう手遅れ？
Even though I'm fine, I'm sighing. Is it perhaps already too late?
でもどっちつかずじゃ動けないから ときめき運んできてね My Sugar
But I can't move if we are in limbo, so bring me some excitement, my sugar.
ちょこちょこ せんせーしょん Yeah!
Choco Choco Sensation, yeah!
絶対君もダメにしたい
I absolutely want to spoil you too!
癒月ちょこ 生誕祭 2026
[Yuzuki Choco Birthday Celebration 2026]
はい！ということで！
Yes! And so...
癒月ちょこ生誕祭2026始まりましたー！
Yuzuki Choco's Birthday Celebration 2026 has begun!
見て見て！1曲目から、ちょこ、生まれ変わりました！
Look, look! Starting from the first song, Choco has been reborn!
いや、今日はね、原点回帰ということで
Well, today we are returning to our roots...
ちょこの、なんと、保健室ステージなの！
so this is Choco's nurse's office stage!
いや、ちょっと保健室もちょっと生まれ変わって、めちゃめちゃ可愛くなりました！
Yes, the nurse's office has also been reborn and become super cute!
シチュエーションドラマとかできそうだよね！
It looks like we could do situation dramas here!
今日は生まれ変わったニューちょこと、素敵なゲスト様をいっぱい呼んで
Today, reborn as New Choco, I've invited many wonderful guests...
ライブをしていくんだけど、その前に
to perform a live show, but before that...
みんな、ちょこのこと、もっと見たいよね？
everyone wants to see more of Choco, right?
あ、でも、まだダメだよ。ふふっ。
Ah, but not yet. Hehe.
これから来るお二人に、ちょこの撮影会をご依頼しちゃいました！
I have requested the two guests who are coming next to hold a photoshoot for Choco!
それでは早速呼んでいきましょう！ノエル様、ラミィ様！
Without further ado, let's call them out! Noel-sama, Lamy-sama!
わー！来たよー！
Yay! We're here!
せーの！ちょこ先生、お誕生日おめでとう！
One, two... Choco-sensei, happy birthday!
ありがとう！嬉しい！
Thank you! I'm so happy!
えー、ということで今回はね、この可愛い両手に花で
Alright, so this time, with flowers in both of my hands...
可愛いお二人に、ちょっとね、ちょこの撮影会をしてってもらおうと思うんですけど
these two cuties will be doing a photoshoot of Choco!
まずは自己紹介よろしくお願いします！ノエちゃんから！
But first, please introduce yourselves! Starting with Noe-chan!
はい！えー、こんまっする！ホロライブ3期生の白銀ノエルと...
Yes! Konmassuru! I'm Shirogane Noel from Hololive Gen 3...
はい！ホロライブ5期生の顔が肝臓、雪花ラミィです！
And I'm Yukihana Lamy from Hololive Gen 5, whose face is a liver!
今日はよろしくお願いします！
Thank you both for being here today!
はーい！まぁね、ちょっとちょこ先生の本当に可愛くなったところを
Yes! Well, Choco-sensei has become so cute...
ちょっと団長頑張って、攻めていこうと思いますので、よろしくお願いします！
and Danchou is going to do her best to capture it, so look forward to it!
攻めて、攻めて！
Aggressive, aggressive!
ラミィも攻めるよね？
Lamy, you're going to push the limits too, right?
ラミィもギリギリを攻めていきたいと思います！
I want to push it right to the absolute limit!
いや、撮影会やるならちょっとね、このお二人を呼ぶしかないかなって思って
If I'm doing a photoshoot, I knew I just had to invite you two...
呼んじゃいました！
so here you are!
嬉しい！
We're so happy!
いや、しかもしかも、ちょっと後で、この3人から
And what's more, the three of us will also have...
なんと、お知らせもあるみたいなので！
an announcement later on!
お知らせ？気になる気になる！
An announcement? I'm so curious!
撮影会の後で、皆様、楽しみにしててください！
It'll be after the photoshoot, so please look forward to it, everyone!
楽しみだー！
We can't wait!
それじゃあちょっと、こちらで撮影会、よろしくお願いします！
Well then, please take care of the photoshoot over here!
行くぞー！
Let's go!
えっほ、えっほ、えっほ...
Step, step, step...
わぁー！なんかすごいとこ来たぞー！すっごい！可愛い！
Wow! We've come to an amazing place! This is awesome! It's so cute!
可愛いでしょう？可愛いでしょう？
Cute, right? Isn't it cute?
撮影会は、ちょこのここの、診察室でやります！
We'll do the photoshoot here in Choco's examination room!
うわー！診察室だ！チョコ先生の診察室！すげー可愛い！
Wow, the examination room! Choco-sensei's examination room! It's super cute!
いいでしょ、いいでしょ！
That's great, that's great!
え、でもさ、診察室だけど、べ、ベッドは？ベッドどこ？
But wait, this is an examination room... Where's the b-bed? Where is it?
ベッド？/ うん。
The bed? / Yeah.
あ、え！なんかパネルもある。/ あ、これ使う？
Oh! There's even a panel. / Ah, should we use this?
あ、そこはダメ！/ え？これダメなの？
Ah, not that one! / Eh? Is this not allowed?
そこは、あとの面談で使うの！
That's for the interview later!
面談！？/ 面談で使うの！？
An interview!? / We use it for an interview!?
ちょっとね、ベッドとか、ちょっと色々、撮影会とか、シチュエーションボイス、ドラマとかやろうかなって。
Well, I was thinking of doing some photoshoots, situation dramas, and other stuff with the bed.
シチュエーションドラマ！？
A situation drama!?
とんでみないことをしようとしてる！/ 本当だよ！
She's trying to do something outrageous! / Seriously!
いやー、そうなんですよ。
Yeah, that's right.
まあね、それは置いておいて。/ あ、置いておくんだ。
Well, putting that aside... / Oh, you're putting it aside.
今回は、お二人に撮影をしてもらいたいので。
This time, I want you two to take photos of me.
まずは... / わかりました。
So first... / Understood.
撮りますよ、よし。
I'm going to take pictures. Alright.
ラミィ様には、カメラ。
For Lamy-sama, a camera.
お、本格的な！すごい、カメラ来た！
Oh, a professional one! Awesome, a camera!
そして、ノエル様にはこちらの、じゃじゃーん。
And for Noel-sama, this... Ta-da!
なんだいこれ？
What is this?
チョコのギリギリを守るために、特別に作られた、モザイク棒です！
To protect Choco's boundaries, this is a specially made mosaic bar!
特別！/ すごい、特別仕様きた！
Special! / Wow, a special version!
なんとこれ、ボタンで、このモザイクの粗さを変えれるらしい。
With this, apparently you can change the intensity of the pixelation with a button!
え、すごい！今めっちゃ粗くなってるから。
Oh, wow! It's super pixelated right now.
あ、本当だ、薄くできる！
Oh, you're right, you can make it lighter!
すげえ、でもなんか粗い方が、むしろいいまであるな、これ。/ 確かに。
Awesome. But actually, maybe the more pixelated, the better. / True.
オッケー、隠せる？これ大丈夫かな、でも配信ね。
Okay, can you block it? I hope this is okay for the stream.
ちょっと守りますよ、チョコの配信を。
I'll protect it. We'll protect Choco's stream.
守ってください。/ がんばります！
Please protect me. / We'll do our best!
それでは、撮影会... スタート！
Well then, let the photoshoot... start!
イェーイ！
Yay!
まずは全身。
First, full body.
そうだね、普通にね、ちょっと。
Yeah, let's start normal.
ポーズ、いつものチョコ先生の。
Your usual pose, Choco-sensei.
こんな感じ？
Like this?
あー、美しい。
Ah, beautiful.
美しい！あ、いい、いい！
Beautiful! Ah, nice, nice!
かわいい！/ え、でも、ここ、ちょっとまずいんじゃないの？ここ。
Cute! / Wait, but isn't this part a bit risky? Right here.
まずいかな？
Is it bad?
逆にいい、逆に！
Actually, it's good! The other way around!
ちょ、団長、ノリノリなんですけど！
Wait, Noel, you're way too into this!
まずいかな？ちょっと、ちょっとね。
Is it risky? Just a little bit...
ちょっとここ揺れてる、めっちゃ！/ モザイクが、モザイクが追いついてない！
It's swaying a lot right here! / The pixelation... The pixelation can't keep up!
追いついてない！じゃ、ノエル様がんばってください！/ がんばります！
It's not keeping up! Noel-sama, do your best! / I will!
こうやってね、こういう感じでね。
Like this, like this...
うん、うん。で。
Yeah, yeah. And...
ちょっと、ジャンプしてもらうの、見てもらっても？/ あ、ジャンプ確かに、すごくぷるん。
Can we see you jump a bit? / Oh, jumping definitely makes it sway.
えいっ、あ、揺れた？/ 揺れた揺れた！めっちゃ揺れた！
Hop! Ah, did it sway? / It swayed, it swayed! It swayed like crazy!
ダメでしょ、これ。/ あらあらあら。
This is bad, right? / Oh dear, oh dear.
え、ちょっと、せっかく生だから、椅子とかもう座っちゃう？/ 椅子？うん、椅子ね、ここに。
Wait, since we're here, why don't you sit on the chair? / The chair? Yeah, the chair is here.
座りますね。/ はい、よいしょ。
She's sitting down. / Okay, there we go.
おお、いいですね。こっちもかわいい！
Oh, nice. This is cute too!
なんか、ちょっと青っぽいんだね。
It's kind of bluish, isn't it?
あ、そう、チョコね、そこが赤なの。
Ah, yes. For Choco, that part is red.
あ、えー！？
Ah, really!?
ちょ、ちょ、ちょ、ちょ... まずい...
Wait, wait, wait... That's risky...
ありがとうございます！/ そこがね、赤なの。これ、こうすると。
Thank you very much! / That part is red. If I do this...
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
大丈夫、あ、でもなんか見えてないからね。
It's okay. Oh, but nothing is showing.
大丈夫です、大丈夫です。守ってます。チャンネル守ってます。
It's fine, it's fine. We're protecting it. Protecting the channel.
いい。じゃあ、こう、どんどん、どんどん、上を、うーん、見てもらって。
Nice. Then, can you gradually look up, like this?
あ、いいですね！
Oh, that's nice!
あら、かわいい？
Oh, is it cute?
見えてる？/ 見えてるよ、見えてるよ！
Can you see? / I see it, I see it!
見えてる？/ かわいいー！
Can you see? / So cute!
いいですね！
That's great!
ちなみに、ラミィさん、あれですよ。この、椅子に座って先生ポーズも、希望してましたけど。
By the way, Lamy also requested the "sensei pose" while sitting on the chair.
あ、そう！先生ポーズとってほしい。
Ah, yes! I want you to strike a sensei pose.
先生ポーズってなんだ？こんな感じ？
What is a sensei pose? Like this?
あー！いい！いいですね！非常に！
Ah! Great! That's very good! Extremely!
でも、これモザイクいらないね、これは。非常に。/ 非常に。
Actually, we don't need the mosaic for this. Extremely. / Extremely.
本当にいらないの？これ。/ いや、わかんない。チョコ先生の魅力が溢れすぎてて。
Do we really not need it? / Well, I don't know. Choco-sensei's charm is just overflowing.
いいですね！/ 素晴らしい！
That's great! / Wonderful!
え、じゃあ団長もいいですか？/ なになに？
Can I ask for one too? / What is it?
お尻フリフリ、ちょっと、していただきたいんで、ちょっと、フリフリ。
I'd like you to wiggle your hips a bit, just a little wiggle.
えーっと、後ろ向いてもらって。/ 後ろ向いて、白衣越しだけど。
Umm, can you turn around? / Turn around, but through the lab coat?
フリフリ。/ あ、いいですね！
Wiggle, wiggle. / Oh, nice!
白衣越しが！
Through the lab coat!
その下に... あ、ちょっと。
Underneath that... Ah, wait...
でもこれ、白衣って、これ脱げ、脱いでほしいんだけど、これ脱げないの？
But wait, can't you take off the lab coat? I want you to take it off.
脱げるけど、面談でって言ってた。
I can take it off, but I said that's for the interview.
あ、面談なら脱いでくれるんですね！
Ah, so you'll take it off for the interview!
え、ガニ股、あの、ココ会長リスペクトで、団長ガニ股好きなんだ。
Wait, how about a crab walk? Out of respect for Coco-kaichou, I love crab walks.
ガニ股？
Crab walk?
うわー！
Whoa!
ガニ股！
Crab walk!
いいですね！ガニ股助かる！
Nice! The crab walk is a lifesaver!
ガニ股！これちょっとモザイクモザイク！
Crab walk! Wait, mosaic, mosaic!
ちょっと見えてるもんな、モザイクお願いします、モザイクがむしろ効果。
It's kind of showing! Mosaic, please! Actually, the mosaic makes it even worse...
やばい！
This is bad!
逆にやばい！やばいやばい。
It's risky in a different way! Oh no, oh no.
かわいい。ふぅー。
Cute. Whew.
どんどんいこう、どんどんいこう。
Let's keep going, let's keep going.
じゃあ、ラストは、やっぱりアイドルだからさ、チョコ先生。アイドル。とびきり可愛いアイドル、お願いします。
Then, for the last one, since you're an idol, Choco-sensei... An idol. Please show us your cutest idol pose.
はいっ。
Okay!
え、かわいい！
Oh, so cute!
いい！
Great!
これ、あ、いい！ね。
This is really good!
ポーズ！
Nice pose!
かわいい！
So cute!
うむ。
Mmh.
アップいい、顔のアップいいね。
Close-up is great, close-up of your face is nice.
たまらんです！
I can't get enough of this!
かわいい！
So cute!
うーん。
Mmm.
オッケー、いっぱいいただいた。
Okay, I got plenty.
ありがとう！
Thank you!
いやちょっとね、この続きはね、ちょっとメン限でやらせていただきますので。
Now, we'll continue this during the members-only stream, so...
メン限ではちょっと歌も、撮影会も、シチュエーションドラマもなんと2本やっちゃいます。
...in the members-only stream, we'll do songs, a photo shoot, and even two situation dramas!
おお！
Oh!
ちなみにさ、タイトルとかあんの？そのシチュエーションドラマって。
By the way, are there titles for those situation dramas?
あ、今回のタイトルが...
Ah, this time's titles are...
先生とベッドで特別バレンタイン
Special Valentine in Bed with the Teacher
えー！特別？ベッドで特別バレンタイン？！
Wh-! Special? Special Valentine in bed?!
あと、診察室で甘い処方箋をっていう...
And also, "A Sweet Prescription in the Exam Room."
甘い！処方箋を！
Sweet! Prescription!
あの、目線もちょっとカメラマンさんをベッドに横たわらせて
Um, the perspective will be like having the cameraman lie on the bed...
ちょっとみんなが本当に見えるように、ちょこが覆いかぶさるように
...so that everyone can really see it like Choco is leaning over them.
ちょっといろんな画角で撮っていきたいと思います。
We want to shoot from various angles.
楽しみ！お楽しみに！
How exciting! Look forward to it!
ということで、そろそろお時間が迫ってきたので、ライブの方に戻りたいと思います。
And with that, it's about time, so we should head back to the live stage.
この気持ちで？！ライブだった？！そうだった！
In this mood?! Oh, we had a live show! That's right!
急げー！
Hurry!
わーい！
Yay!
はーい！というわけで、このあと二人それぞれ、ちょっとデュエットしてもらうんだけど。
Yes! And so, next we have two duets coming up, but...
ちょっとね、最後に三人でも歌うので楽しみにしといてください。
...we'll also sing together as a trio at the very end, so please look forward to it!
楽しみ！それでお着替えに行ましょう。
Can't wait! Now, let's go change our outfits.
お、これ？すごい！リボンもついてる。かわいい。
Oh, is this it? Amazing! It even has ribbons. So cute.
じゃ、ちょっとカーテンの裏でお着替え行ってきます。
Well then, we'll go change behind the curtain.
それでは聴いてください。
Now, please listen to...
サマーチョコレート
Summer chocolate
そろそろ そばに darling baby
It's about time, come close to me, darling baby
とろけちゃって catch me darling
Melt away and catch me, darling
ピュア ピュア ココア ふんわり
Pure, pure cocoa, so fluffy
チュル チュル
Slurp, slurp
ワン・ツー！
One, two!
なんか眠れない夜には
On those nights when I can't sleep
お散歩
I go for a walk
特別パーティータイム
A special party time
2人きり
Just the two of us
あの角曲がれば ベンチしかない公園だよ
If we turn that corner, there's a park with only a bench
蒸し暑い空気の中 迷い込むんだ
We wander into the muggy air
コンビニちょっと寄り道
A quick detour to the convenience store
甘い投資
A sweet investment
アイスじゃなくて これがいい
Not ice cream, this is what I want
炭酸お酒 ほろ酔い
Fizzy alcohol, feeling slightly tipsy
ウィンクでストロング リキュールじゃもう酔えない
A wink and a strong drink, liqueurs won't get me drunk anymore
ラムで潰して お願い
Knock me out with rum, please
お砂糖増し増しで
With extra, extra sugar
飲みやすさとかいらない
I don't need it to be easy to drink
灼熱でさ 溶かして
Melt it in the scorching heat
ゴクって飲んで
Take a big gulp
クセのある私のことを
Take care of me
大事にしてよね
even with all my quirks, okay?
サマーチョコレート
Summer chocolate
そろそろ そばに darling baby
It's about time, come close to me, darling baby
とろけちゃって catch me darling
Melt away and catch me, darling
ピュア ピュア ココア ふんわり
Pure, pure cocoa, so fluffy
チュル チュル
Slurp, slurp
ワン・ツー！
One, two!
ちょっと寂しい帰り道
On the slightly lonely walk home
ふらふら
Wobbling around
特別ボーナスタイム
A special bonus time
手を繋ごう
Let's hold hands
大きめTシャツ 君に借りたの羽織って
Wearing the oversized T-shirt I borrowed from you
匂わせみたいにして 困らせたいんだ
I want to tease you and make you flustered
コンビニまた寄っちゃって
Stopping by the convenience store again
楽しい
How fun
もう1本だけの
Just one more bottle of
弱いやつ
a weak one
うるうるに見えるキミ
you, looking all teary-eyed
テンパリングが大事
Tempering is important!
アツすぎても飽きちゃって
Even if it's too hot, I get tired of it.
冷たいのはダメ
And cold is no good.
やだもん
No way!
チョコみたいな私を
Make me, who is like chocolate...
プレシャスにして扱って
...precious, and treat me well.
微炭酸のお酒で
With a slightly carbonated drink...
しゅわしゅわしゅわ
...fizz, fizz, fizz.
愛は伝えなきゃ届かない
Love won't reach unless you express it.
恋してる証拠に
As proof that I'm in love,
ここでちゅーってして
give me a kiss right here!
夜空のグラスに
In the night sky glass,
キラキラ零して
spill sparkling lights.
息もできないくらいにもう
So much that I can't even breathe,
だって... だって... だって...
because... because... because...
恋に溺れて
I'm drowning in love.
君の熱で溶けたら
If I melt from your warmth,
そのまんまで食べてよ
eat me just like that.
手にベトベト付いちゃって
Getting all sticky on your hands,
一生いっしょ保存版
we'll be together forever.
缶のお酒ほろ酔い
Slightly drunk on canned alcohol,
ウインクですとろんぐ！
strong with a wink!
リキョールじゃもう酔えない
Liqueur can't make me drunk anymore.
ラブで潰して お願い
Crush me with love, please!
お砂糖はマシマシで
With extra, extra sugar,
飲みやすさとかいらない
I don't care if it's easy to drink.
灼熱でさ、溶かして？
Melt it in the scorching heat, okay?
ごくって飲んで
Gulp it down!
クセのある私だからさ
Because I'm a bit quirky,
君が選ばれた
you were chosen.
サマーチョコレート
Summer Chocolate!
どろどろ とろり べいっび
Melty, gooey baby,
とろけちゃって catch me だーりん
melting away, catch me darling.
ぴゅあぴゅあ ここあ ふわり きゅるきゅる
Pure, pure cocoa, soft and swirling.
ワン、ツー！
One, two!
What's up, Japan?!
Can you hear me?!
It's already a hot night.
No money, no job?
Too much bad news.
We have no reason to be down!
It's time to get up!
We have a hot new song,
that's from AKB48,
to make you feel good!
Koi Suru Fortune Cookie!
So dance, Japan, crazy!
恋するフォーチュンクッキー
Koi Suru Fortune Cookie
あなたのこと好きなのに
Even though I'm in love with you,
私にまるで興味ない
you have absolutely no interest in me.
何度目かの失恋の準備
I'm getting ready for yet another heartbreak.
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
まわりを見れば大勢の
If I look around me,
可愛いコたちがいるんだもん
there are so many cute girls.
地味な花は気づいてくれない
You won't notice a plain flower like me.
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
カフェテリア流れるMusic
With music playing in the cafeteria,
ぼんやり聴いていたら
as I listlessly listen to it...
知らぬ間にリズムに合わせ
Before I know it, matching the rhythm,
つま先から動き出す
my feet start moving from my toes.
止められない今の気持ち
I can't stop this feeling now!
カモナカモナカモナカモナベイビー
Come on, come on, come on, come on, baby!
占ってよ
Tell my fortune!
恋するフォーチュンクッキー！
My love is in a fortune cookie!
未来はそんな悪くないよ
The future won't be so bad.
Hey! Hey! Hey!
ツキを呼ぶには笑顔を見せること
To bring in luck, just show a big smile.
ハートのフォーチュンクッキー
In my heart is a fortune cookie,
運勢今日よりもよくしよう
let's make my fate better than today.
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
人生捨てたもんじゃないよね
Life is not something to throw away, right?
あっと驚く奇跡が起きる
A surprising miracle will happen!
あなたとどこかで愛し合える予感
I have a feeling we'll love each other somewhere.
あなたにちゃんとコクりたい
I want to confess my feelings to you properly,
だけど自分に自信ない
but I don't have enough confidence in myself.
リアクションは想像つくから
Because I can already imagine your reaction...
イェーイ イェーイ イェーイ
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
性格いい子がいいなんて
Boys say that they prefer a girl
男の子は言うけど
with a good personality, but...
ルックスがアドバンテージ
Having good looks is always an advantage.
いつだって可愛い子が
In the end, it's always the cute girl
人気投票 1位になる
who wins first place in the popularity poll.
プリーズ プリーズ プリーズ オーベイビー
Please, please, please, oh baby,
私も見て
look at me too!
恋するフォーチュンクッキー
The Fortune Cookie in Love!
その殻 さあ壊してみよう
Come on, let's break open its shell!
ヘイ ヘイ ヘイ
Hey, hey, hey!
先の展開 神様も知らない
Even God doesn't know how things will turn out next!
涙のフォーチュンクッキー
The tearful Fortune Cookie!
そんなにネガティブにならずに
Don't be so negative!
ヘイ ヘイ ヘイ ヘイ ヘイ ヘイ
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
世界は愛で溢れているよ
The world is filled with love, you know?
悲しい出来事忘れさせる
It makes you forget all the sad things.
明日は明日の風が吹くと思う
I believe tomorrow is another day.
カモン カモン カモン カモン ベイビー
Come on, come on, come on, come on, baby!
占ってよ
Tell my fortune!
恋するフォーチュンクッキー
The Fortune Cookie in Love!
未来はそんなに悪くないよ
The future isn't actually that bad!
ヘイ ヘイ ヘイ
Hey, hey, hey!
ツキを呼ぶには 笑顔を見せること
To bring good luck, just show a smile!
ハートのフォーチュンクッキー
The heart's Fortune Cookie!
運勢 今日よりも良くしよう
Let's make our luck better than today!
ヘイ ヘイ ヘイ ヘイ ヘイ ヘイ
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
人生捨てたもんじゃないよね
Life isn't all that bad, is it?
あっと驚く奇跡が起きる
A wonderful, surprising miracle will happen!
あなたとどこかで愛し合える予感
I have a feeling we'll fall in love somewhere!
キミが好きったらキミが好き
When I say I like you, I like you!
When we say we like you, we like you!
ぴゅわら ぴゅわら ぴゅわら ぴゅわらっ
Pyuwara, pyuwara, pyuwara, pyuwaratt!
あのね 乙女は本気出すとすごいんです
You know, a maiden is amazing when she gets serious!
ワン ツー いずれ出動
One, two, soon to mobilize!
あの手この手でライバルを出し抜くの
Pulling out all the stops to outsmart the rivals.
全部計算済みレシピ通り
Everything is calculated, just as the recipe says!
好きだって武器に満ち満ちて
Filled with love, our ultimate weapon!
手際よく煮詰めたりして
Skillfully boiling it down...
うっとりで甘えて
Sweetly spoiling you in a daze...
すでにデリシャス
Already delicious!
あー焦げちゃったー
Ah, it's burnt!
つまみ食いしたらなくなった！
I snuck a bite and now it's gone!
うるんで日本酒
Teary eyes and Japanese sake!
時にファンキー
Sometimes funky!
苦いのはNGで
Bitter things are a total no-go!
女の子の季節だもん 全部
Since it's a girl's season, everything...
思い通りになってよね
...must go exactly as we wish!
キミは私と結ばれます
You are bound to end up with me!
本命あげちゃう メルティ
I'll give you my true feelings, meltingly!
誰にも渡さない大戦争
A great war where I won't hand you to anyone!
溶けちゃいます メルティ
Melting away, melting!
そら手と手繋いじゃう 内緒ねと
See, we're holding hands, "keep it a secret!"
スウィーティ・スウィーティ・キス
Sweetie, sweetie, kiss!
甘くていいの？
Is it okay to be sweet?
スウィーティ・スウィーティ・ハート
Sweetie, sweetie, heart!
こういうのがいいっしょ
This kind of style is good, right?
らぶこいなんだもん
Because it's lovey-dovey!
絶対譲らない覚悟です
We're fully prepared to never give you up!
本気なのです
We're totally serious!
目を見て言って
Look into my eyes and say it...
キミの気持ち
...your true feelings!
ぴゅわら ぴゅわら ぴゅわら ぴゅわらっ
Pyuwara, pyuwara, pyuwara, pyuwaratt!
ガールズ・バトル・フィー
Girls' Battle Fie...
なんでちょこと喋ってんの？
Why are you talking to Choco?!
ガールズ・バトル・フィー
Girls' Battle Fie...
意思疎通がショート！
Communication short-circuit!
ガールズ・バトル・フィー
Girls' Battle Fie...
大丈夫、へこたれないもん！
It's okay, I won't lose heart!
惚れさせたら勝ちです
Making you fall in love is a win!
甘いパルフェを食べちゃいな？
Why don't you eat some sweet parfait?
砂糖の量は愛の量！
The amount of sugar is the amount of love!
間違えた、これ塩だった！
I made a mistake, this was salt!
マボランシン
Maboranshin!
調理中ドキドキしてはいる
While cooking, my heart is pounding...
真心込めてラッピング
...wrapping it with all my heart!
自分も本気コーデでいく
I'm going with my best outfit too!
祈るラブチャ
Praying for love...
何度も試作した 予行練習もした
I made prototypes over and over, and even did dress rehearsals.
弱気になどなるな
Don't you dare lose heart!
大丈夫自分史上1番 かわいい私なんだから
It's okay, because I'm the cutest version of myself in history!
君は私と結ばれます
You will end up with me.
結ばれる運命なのです
It is our destiny to be bound together.
本命あげちゃうめるてぃー！
I'm giving you my true love, Melty!
誰にも渡さない大戦争
The great war of not letting anyone else have you.
ときめいちゃいます？めるしー♡
Are you feeling butterflies? Merci!
それじゃ手とか繋いじゃう？ 内緒のデート
Then shall we hold hands? On our secret date.
すぅぃーてぃー すぅぃーてぃー キス
Sweetie, sweetie, kiss...
甘くていいの
It's okay if it's sweet.
すぅぃーてぃー すぅぃーてぃー ハグ
Sweetie, sweetie, hug...
こういうのがいいっしょ？
This is what you want, right?
初恋なんだもん 絶対譲らない覚悟です
Since it's my first love, I'm determined to never yield.
本気なのです
I am truly serious.
目を見て言って？ 君の気持ち
Look into my eyes and tell me... your feelings.
ぴゅあら ぴゅあら ぴゅあら ぴゅあらぶ
Pure-a, pure-a, pure-a, pure-a love
ぴゅあら ぴゅあらぶ
Pure-a, pure love!
はーい！ということで
All right! And with that...
チョコたち3人の新曲でしたー！
...that was the new song by the three of us!
いぇーい！新曲でしたー！
Yay! It was our new song!
改めまして、ノエル様、ラミィ様と一緒にね
Once again, this is in collaboration with...
コラボ歌唱をした『初恋大戦争』という新曲なんですけど
...Noel-sama and Lamy-sama, called 'Hatsukoi Daisensou'.
今回、作詞・作曲をめだんし様、そして編曲をよおふ様にお願いいたしました！
This time, lyrics/music are by medansy-sama and arrangement is by Yoofu-sama!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
いや、今回のテーマが、バレンタインの日に
The theme of this song is on Valentine's Day...
3人の可愛い女の子たちが、1人の男の子を手に入れるために
...three cute girls clash fiercely to win over a single boy...
バチバチにね、出し抜こうとするみたいな
...trying to outsmart each other.
激甘なテーマ楽曲となっております！
It's an incredibly sweet theme song!
いいですね！かわいい！
It's nice, right? So cute!
そう！いやもう3人の声が合わさって
Yes! Our three voices blend together so well...
めちゃめちゃアイドルソングになっているので、ぜひぜひ聞いてください！
...making it a wonderful idol song, so please listen to it!
聞いてね！何回も聞きたいね！
Please listen! I want to hear it over and over!
何回も聴き直したい！
I want to replay it again and again!
こちらの楽曲、この後24時から
This song will be distributed...
2月15日0時からね、各種音楽サイトにて配信されます！
...on various music platforms starting from 24:00 tonight!
やったー！
Hooray!
聞ける！
We can listen to it!
そしてね、なんと！この配信後、すぐに
And what's more, right after this release...
この楽曲のMVが...公開されます！
...the music video for this song... will be published!
やったー！
Yay!
嬉しい！
I'm so happy!
いや、ぜひぜひ皆様、いっぱい聴いて
So, we hope everyone listens to it a lot...
MVの方にも感想とかね、コメントいただけたら嬉しいかなって思います！
...and leaves comments with your thoughts on the MV!
よろしくお願いします！
We look forward to it!
じゃあね、2人とも、今日はありがとう！
Well then, thank you both for today!
お誕生日おめでとう！
Happy birthday!
ありがとう、嬉しい！
Thank you, I'm so happy!
引き続きね、見守ってください！
Please continue to watch over me!
頑張ってね！頑張る！ありがとう！
Good luck! I will! Thank you!
おさらば！おさらば！
Goodbye! Farewell!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
そして、ここからライブ後半となります！
And from here, we enter the second half of the live!
まだまだ、ゲストパートとか
We still have guest performances...
なんと最後に重大告知もあるので
...and even a major announcement at the end...
皆様、一緒に楽しんでいきましょう！
...so let's keep enjoying it together, everyone!
それでは、次のゲストは...こちら！
Now then, our next guest is... this person!
大人なフリして。 作詞・作曲 : s-num
[Title: Pretending to Be Mature. / Lyrics & Music: s-num]
急に「会いたい」って いつものように準備してる
When you suddenly say 'I want to see you,' I get ready just like always.
午前0時過ぎの終電で向かうって返信した
I replied that I'll head over on the last train past midnight.
「やめときなよ」って言われ...
Even if I'm told, 'You should stop,'...
また会いに行く 会いたいから
I will go to see you again, because I want to see you.
別々に落ち合う街の風は少し冷たい
The wind in the town where we meet separately is a bit cold.
慣れないワイン無理やり飲みほしてしまってはふらふわ
Forcing down wine I'm not used to, I'm feeling all dizzy.
嫌われちゃったらどうしよう
What if you end up hating me?
下手にしちゃったらどうしよう
What if I mess up?
少しも残したくない
I don't want to leave even a single drop.
ちょっと期待して、ねぇ
I'm expecting a little bit, hey.
ずっと見栄張って、ねぇ
I've been keeping up appearances, hey.
周りばかり気にして生きている
Living life constantly worrying about everyone around me.
ちょっと優越感でも
Even with a slight sense of superiority,
なんか寂しくて あぁ
somehow it's lonely, ah...
本当の自分じゃない気がして
Feeling like this isn't the real me.
いつも分かったフリして
Always pretending to understand,
そんなんじゃないのに無理して
forcing myself when that's not how it is.
味のしないキスでも
Even if it's a tasteless kiss,
やっぱ一番嬉しくて
it's still what makes me happiest.
取り繕った私はかわいいかな
Is the groomed, made-up me cute?
今夜は壊れるほど抱きしめて
Hold me so tight tonight that I might break.
今にも切れそうな糸で繋がってる恋だね
This love is connected by a thread that could break at any moment.
私が諦めたらきっと簡単に消えちゃうね
If I give up, I'm sure it will easily vanish.
引き止めるにはどうする？
What should I do to hold you back?
あの子だったらどうする？
What would that other girl do?
不器用に指を絡めて
Clumsily intertwining our fingers.
いつもチェックして、ねぇ
Always checking, hey.
一喜一憂で、ねぇ
Swinging between joy and sorrow, hey.
他の子と比べてばかりいた
I was always comparing myself to other girls.
一番見て欲しい、あぁ
I want you to look at me the most, ah...
目の前のあなたは、あぁ
The you right in front of me, ah...
どこか違う景色見てる？
Are you looking at some other scenery?
いつも優しいフリして
Always pretending to be kind,
そんなんじゃないのに笑って
smiling even though that's not how it is.
近づけば近づくほど
The closer I get to you,
心は遠く感じて
the further away your heart feels.
少しずつ離れてくことわかるよ
I can tell that we're slowly drifting apart.
今夜は忘れるほど抱きしめて
Hold me tonight so tight that I'll forget everything.
自分がもっと強ければ
If only I were stronger,
サヨナラを言えるのにな
I would be able to say goodbye.
いつも分かったフリして
Always pretending to understand,
そんなんじゃないのに無理して
forcing myself when that's not how it is.
ふと見せる優しさが
The kindness you suddenly show,
ずっと忘れられなくて
I can't ever forget it.
取り繕った私はかわいいかな
Is the groomed, made-up me cute?
今夜は壊れるほど抱きしめて
Hold me so tight tonight that I might break.
突然溢れ出した雨
The rain that suddenly started pouring down.
私頑張ったよね
I tried my best, didn't I?
いつか振り向いてくれると思っていた
I thought that you'd look back at me someday.
もういいかな
Is it enough now?
取り繕った私が流れてゆく
The groomed, made-up me is washing away.
今夜は忘れるほど抱きしめて
Hold me tonight so tight that I'll forget everything.
chocolate box
[Song: chocolate box]
なんかいつも眠そうだし
You always seem sleepy somehow,
なんかいつもつまんなそうだし
and you always seem bored somehow,
なんかいつもヤバそうだし
and you always seem crazy somehow,
なんかいつもスマホいじってるし
and you're always messing with your smartphone.
ホントはテンション高いのに
Even though you're usually high-energy,
アタシといると超低いし
you're super low-energy when you're with me.
なんなん自分？ありえなくない？
What is up with you? Isn't that unbelievable?
嫌い、大嫌い。どうでもいい！！
I hate you, I really hate you. I don't care anymore!
だったらボクも言うけどさぁ
Well, then I'll say something too!
ちっちゃい事ですぐ怒るし
You get angry over tiny things immediately,
言い返したらすぐ泣くし
and you cry immediately if I talk back,
ごめんって言っても許してくれないし
and you won't forgive me even if I say sorry.
その割一夜が明ければ
But despite that, once morning comes,
ケロっとおはようとか言うし
you casually say good morning like nothing happened.
あぁなんて罪深い人なんだ
Ah, what a sinful person you are.
畜生！！もう知らないぞ！！
Dammit! I don't care about you anymore!
甘い 甘い 恋の魔法 箱
A sweet, sweet magic box of love.
宇宙 味の秘密のチョコレート
A secret chocolate with the flavor of the universe.
コレーションを 切り分けて 彩って食べちゃおうか
...rations, let's slice them up, color them, and eat!
苦い苦い愛の玉手箱
A bitter, bitter treasure box of love,
未来味の不思議なチョコレート
mysterious chocolates with the taste of the future.
温めて 混ぜたらきっと
If we warm them up and mix them,
いつかお口に合う味になるの
surely they'll suit your taste one day.
ねえねえ、チョコ以外がなーんだ？
Hey, hey, what is it besides chocolate?
さっきはあのね、ごめんね
Um, sorry about earlier.
何が？
For what?
いつもモヤモヤってなるじゃん
Things always get a bit awkward, you know.
それで？
And?
今日はこれを渡したくて
So I wanted to give you this today.
言葉じゃ足りないからさ
Words aren't really enough, so...
だから？
So?
受け取ってくれないかな
Would you accept it?
何を？
Accept what?
一緒にいてくれてありがとう
Thank you for being with me.
おーーー！
Ohhh!
分かったよそれ
I accept it!
あなたの優しさに ついつい甘えちゃう
I end up taking your kindness for granted.
誰よりも近いから 素原になれない
Because you're closer than anyone, I can't be honest.
君の一生懸命さを ついつい忘れちゃう
I end up forgetting how hard you try.
誰よりも一番 大好きなのに
Even though I love you more than anyone.
甘い甘い夢の宝箱
A sweet, sweet treasure box of dreams,
奇跡味の内緒のチョコレート
secret chocolates with the taste of miracles.
二人だけのイノベーションを
Let's search for an innovation
探し組み立てたら逃げようか
just for the two of us, build it, and run away!
苦い苦い日々の化粧箱
A bitter, bitter vanity case of daily life,
世界味の最初のチョコレート
the first chocolates with the taste of the world.
冷めきって割れないように
Lest it gets completely cold and breaks,
大事に包んで 生涯の完成は...って
wrap it carefully... Is it a lifetime masterpiece?
いつだって
At all times,
病めるときも
whether in sickness
どんな日も
or on any day,
そうずっと
yes, always,
健やかなるときも
and in health,
手をとって
holding hands,
違う二人を分かち合うまで
until our two different selves share everything.
愛してる
I love you.
僕もそうさ
So do I.
そばにいて
Stay by my side.
そばにいる
I'm by your side.
なんて嘘かもよ
...Well, that might be a lie!
あ、そうかい
Oh, really?
僕も適当に言った
I was just teasing too.
甘い甘い
Sweet, sweet,
苦い苦い
bitter, bitter.
甘い甘い恋の魔法箱
A sweet, sweet magic box of love,
宇宙味の秘密のチョコレート
secret chocolates with the taste of the universe.
二人だけのデコレーションを
Let's sprinkle decorations
ちりばめて彩って食べちゃおうか
just for the two of us and eat them up!
苦い苦い愛の玉手箱
A bitter, bitter treasure box of love,
未来味の不思議なチョコレート
mysterious chocolates with the taste of the future.
温めて混ぜたらきっと
If we warm them up and mix them, surely
いつか最高に幸せな味になるの
they'll taste like the ultimate happiness one day.
いっせーので
Ready, set, go!
Thank you so much!
See you next time!
ねえ、ひとつだけ聞いていい？
Hey, can I ask you just one thing?
私のこと...
About me...
告白日和、です！
[Song: Kokuhaku Biyori, desu!]
会えるかも今日は 心が騒いで
Maybe we'll meet today, my heart is racing
スキップしたくなった
I felt like skipping along
ときめきに踊る瞬間
in this moment of dancing excitement.
私のことなど
You probably don't
たぶん気にしてないのだけど
give me a second thought, but...
ここにいるんだよ
I'm right here,
私はここよ
I'm right here beside you!
自信が揺れ動く
My confidence is wavering,
嫌われてないかな？
I wonder if you dislike me?
勢いでとにかく挨拶だ！
I'll just muster up the courage to say hello!
やっと晴れたね
It finally cleared up!
ぱーっと晴れたね
Brightly cleared up!
そして元気になるね
And it cheers me up!
おはようの代わりに背中を叩いて
Tapping your back instead of saying good morning,
「さあ、行くよ！」
"Let's go!"
やっと晴れたら
Now that it's finally cleared up,
ぱーっと晴れたら
brightly cleared up,
きっと元気な笑顔
I'm sure we'll have bright smiles!
なんだか
Somehow,
今のこの気持ちが切なくなったよ
this feeling I have right now has become so bittersweet.
授業も上の空
My mind wanders during class
遠くを眺めた
as I gaze into the distance.
恋って甘いもんじゃない？
Isn't love supposed to be sweet?
違うかも つらさ半分
Or maybe not... sharing the pain cuts it in half,
夢見るだけより
Rather than just dreaming,
触って確かめなきゃだから
I have to touch and make sure, so...
だから... 動きだそうよ
So... let's take action!
自分らしくね
In your own way,
楽しく生きるの
live happily!
毎日が奇跡
Every day is a miracle.
言わずに悔やむより勇気だそう
Rather than regretting staying silent, let's have courage!
ずっと前から
Since a long time ago,
うんと前から
since way back when,
聞いてみたくて待ってた
I've been waiting to ask you.
私から最初に
I'll be the first to tell you...
伝えてしまえ 大好きです
I love you so much!
ずっと前だよ
Since a long time ago,
うんと前だよ
since way back when,
聞いたことに答えて
answer what I asked.
どんなふうに感じてるの
How do you feel about me?
全部見せてよ
Show me everything!
楽しく生きるの
live happily!
毎日が奇跡
Every day is a miracle.
本当は不安でも勇気だそう
Even if we're actually anxious, let's have courage!
だそう！うん！
Let's do it! Yeah!
ずっと前から
Since a long time ago,
うんと前から
since way back when,
聞いてみたくて待ってた
I've been waiting to ask you.
私から最初に
I'll be the first to tell you...
伝えてしまえ 大好きです
I love you so much!
ずっと前だよ
Since a long time ago,
うんと前だよ
since way back when,
聞いたことに答えて
answer what I asked.
どんなふうに感じてるの
How do you feel about me?
全部見せてよ
Show me everything!
世界は恋に落ちている
The world is falling in love,
光の矢胸を射す
an arrow of light pierces my heart.
君を分かりたいんだよ
I want to understand you.
ねえ、教えて
Hey, tell me.
世界は恋に落ちている
作詞・作曲：HoneyWorks
[Title: The World is Falling in Love / Lyrics & Composition: HoneyWorks]
すれ違う言葉にちょっとだけの後悔
With just a little regret over words passing by,
涙こぼれて
tears begin to spill.
忙しい感情 鼓動にリンクする
My busy feelings link up with my heartbeat,
チューニング 確かめたいんだ
I want to make sure we're in tune.
目的ばっかにとらわれて
Trapped only by my destination,
大事なものが霞んで逃げて
the important things grew hazy and ran away,
今日もリスタート
and I'm restarting again today.
世界は恋に落ちている
The world is falling in love,
光の矢胸を射す
an arrow of light pierces my heart.
全部分かりたいんだよ
I want to understand everything.
ねえ、聞かせて
Hey, let me hear it.
たった1ミリが遠くて
Just one millimeter feels so far away,
駆け抜けた日々に
in the days we ran through.
忘れない忘れない
I won't forget, I can't forget
輝く1ページ
this shining page.
お似合いの二人になんだか複雑な
To us as a well-matched pair, I somehow have
気持ちがいるよ
complicated feelings.
初めての感情 鼓動にリンクする
This first-time feeling links up with my heartbeat.
体温計
I wonder if my thermometer...
壊れちゃったかな
...has broken down.
自分のこと...
Not even knowing my own...
...しちゃったな
...and gave her advice.
自分のことわからないまま
I still don't even understand myself,
あの個にアドバイスまでしちゃって
yet I went ahead and gave her advice.
胸が痛いや
My chest hurts so much.
世界は恋に落ちている
The whole world is falling in love,
光の矢胸を射す
an arrow of light shoots through my heart.
気付いたこの想いは
These feelings I've realized...
もう、遅いの
...are "already too late."
あのこの方が可愛いの
She is much cuter than me,
知ってるよだけど
I know that, but still...
上手くいかないでなんてね
thinking "I hope it doesn't go well"...
逃げ出したくせに
even though I'm the one who ran away.
バカ
Idiot!
君のこと全部わかりたいって思っちゃう
I want to know everything about you,
これが恋だって初めて気づいたの
I've realized for the first time that this is love.
絶対振り向いてほしい
I definitely want you to look my way.
遅かったけど諦めたくない
I know I'm late, but I don't want to give up!
だって
Because...
好きだから
I love you!
春に咲いた
The flower that bloomed in spring
花が恋をした
fell in love.
花は必死に
The flower desperately
上を向いて笑った
looked up and smiled.
青い夏の
A bud in the blue
つぼみも恋をした
summer also fell in love.
咲かない花と
An unblooming flower and
火薬の匂い
the scent of gunpowder.
ホントの気持ち言葉にして
If I can turn my true feelings into words
大事なこと話せたら
and say what's important,
今日もリスタート
I'll restart again today.
鈍感な君だから
Since you're so dense,
口に出さなきゃ
I have to come out and say it,,
今君に伝えるよ
I'll tell you now...
ねえ
"Hey,"
好きです
I love you.
世界は恋に落ちている
The whole world is falling in love,
光の矢胸を射す
an arrow of light shoots through my heart.
全部わかりたいんだよ
I want to understand everything!
ねえ、聞かせて
"Hey, let me hear it."
手繰り寄せてもうゼロセンチ
I have reeled us in to zero centimeters,
駆け抜けた青春に
in these days of youth passing us by...
忘れない忘れられない
...I won't forget, I can't forget
輝く1ページ
this shining page.
はーい！ということで！
Okay! And with that...
ここまで、アキ様、ロボ子、
up until now, Aki-sama, Roboco,
ござるに...
Gozaru...
ふーちゃんと一緒に歌わせていただきました！
...and Fuu-chan sang together with me!
みんなありがとう！
Thank you, everyone!
さてさて、ここからは、
Now then, from here on...
なんと重大告知が２つあります！
...there are actually two major announcements!
まず１つ目が...
First, the first one is...
こちら！ドドン！
...this! Ta-dah!
癒月ちょこ誕生日記念2026！
Yuzuki Choco Birthday Celebration 2026!
それでは、ちょっと詳しくご紹介していきたいと思います！
So, let me introduce the details to you!
まずはこちら！
First up is this!
ちょこのクッション！
Choco's cushion!
いやこれね、いやちょっとちょこの誕生日といえば、
Well, this, you know, when it comes to Choco's birthday,
毎年、Nardack先生ありがとうございます！ということで、
every year, I say 'Thank you, Nardack-sensei!' and...
今年もNardack先生に、めちゃめちゃ素敵なイラスト描き下ろしていただきました！
...this year too, Nardack-sensei drew a super lovely illustration for me!
今回のテーマはバレンタインということで、
This year's theme is Valentine's Day,
ちょっとね、チョコメイトを抱きながら、
so here I am, holding Chocomate...
ちょっと今回はチョコレート風のクッションにしてみました！
...and we made it a chocolate-bar style cushion this time!
可愛いでしょ！
Isn't it cute?
サイズ感がちょうど、枕くらいになってるので、
The size is just about right to use as a pillow,
ちょっとねお昼寝の時とか仮眠用に、スヤァってできる感じで使えちゃいます！
so you can use it for a quick nap or rest to sleep soundly!
そして続いてはこちら！
And next up is this!
なんと今回初めてちょっと...
Wow, this time, for the first time...
お菓子が作れる...
you can actually make sweets!
なんとなんとチョコのチョコレート型！
And what do we have here? It's Choco's chocolate mold!
耐熱も冷却も、温かいのも
It's heat-resistant and freezer-safe,
冷たいのも両方使えちゃって。
so it can be used for both hot and cold treats.
ちょっとね、チョコと、チョコメイトの
This time, the chocolate mold features
今回はチョコレート型になっております。
shapes of both Choco and Chocomates.
まあマフィンとかね、クッキーとか、
You can use it for muffins, cookies,
あとはまあ普通に冷やし固めてチョコレート入れたりとか、
or just simply pouring in chocolate to let it set.
なんか色々使えるからぜひみんなも作ってみてね！
It's super versatile, so please try making something!
そして続いてはこちら！お待たせしました！
And next up is this! Sorry to keep you waiting!
チョコのすやすやぬいぐるみキーホルダー！
Choco's Sleeping Plushie Keyholder!
まあチョコと言えばね、睡眠ということで、
Since sleep is Choco's specialty,
超ロングスリーパーのチョコが、
as a super long sleeper,
今回はぬいぐるみキーホルダーとなって、
I decided to make a plushie keyholder,
ちょっとすやすやぬいぐるみで作らせていただきました。
specifically a cute sleeping plushie version this time!
まあずっとね、肌身離さず持っていればいつか聞こえてくるかもしれない！
If you keep it close to you all the time, you might hear me yawning one day!
そして、今年もございます。
And we have it again this year.
ユズチョコ勝ち越し台本の、耳舐めASMR台本！
The legendary Choco script, an ear-licking ASMR script!
撮りましたよ、チョコのASMRボイス。
I've recorded Choco's ASMR voices.
今回ね、耳舐めの方は3つございます。
There are three ear-licking tracks this time.
1つ目が、「溶けかけのチョコレート」。
The first one is "Melting Chocolate."
いや、こちらはね、ちょっとあの、
Well, this one...
皆様がご想像してるより、
might actually be a bit more suggestive...
ちょっとあの、あの、エッチかもしれないんですけど。
than you might expect...
配信ではね、絶対にできないボイスとなっておりますので、
Since it's a voice track I could never do on stream,
ぜひともね、皆様、ご購入して聞いてみてください。
please purchase and listen to it!
そして、もう1つが、「残業あとのご褒美デザート」ということで。
And next, "Reward Dessert After Overtime."
こちらはね、チョコとの同棲シチュエーションとなっております。
This is a living-together scenario with Choco.
はい、チョコが残業してきて
Yes, Choco comes home...
帰ってきたときの...保存
after working overtime...
うん、まあデザートは、チョコなのか、君なのか、どっちなんだろうね？保存
Well, is the dessert Choco, or is it you? I wonder which it is.
まあちょっと聞いてみてよ！保存
Well, listen and find out!
そしてそして、
And next,
「年下幼馴染のツンデレバレンタイン」ということで。
"Tsundere Valentine with a Younger Childhood Friend."
今回はね、聞いている君たちがちょっと
This time, listen to it as if you're...
隣の家のお兄ちゃんになった気分で聞いてみてください。
the older brother next door.
こちらもね、耳舐めボイスとなっておりますが、
This is also an ear-licking voice track,
なんとこちら、
but for this one...
ドMの方は絶対に聞いていただけたら、ちょっとニコニコしちゃうんじゃないかなって思います。
if you are a masochist, listening to this will definitely make you grin!
そしてそして、フルセットをご購入の方、フルセット特典！
And next, for those who purchase the full set, here is the bonus! Jacks!
今回はなんと初めてチェキ風ブロマイドカードになりました！
For the first time ever, it's an instax-style photo card!
ちょっとこちらね、数量限定で
The limited-edition version comes with...
直筆サイン＆箔押し複製メッセージが入っております。
a handwritten autograph and foil-stamped message.
カキカキしちゃうよ！
I'll sign them all!
通常バージョンは、箔押し複製サインと複製メッセージが入ります。
The standard version has a printed autograph and message.
そしてね、特典がもう1つ！
And there's one more bonus!
フルセット購入特典として、
As a full set purchase bonus...
ヤキモチのギュッとASMRボイスが入っております。保存
A "Jealous Hug" ASMR voice track is included.
いや、こちらはね、ちょっとあの、甘々のギュッボイスなので、
This is a super sweet hugging voice track,
まあちょっとね、普段はチョコ、嫉妬しないんですけど、
and while Choco doesn't usually get jealous,
ちょっとまあ何に嫉妬してるかは聞いてからのお楽しみなんですけど。
you'll have to listen to find out what I'm jealous of!
ちょっとぜひぜひ、ニヤニヤしながら聞いといてください。ぜひ手に入れてください！
Please listen to it while grinning! Be sure to get it!
そしてそして！
And next!
重大告知2つ目は...
The second major announcement is...
こちら！
this!
ねぇ、ちょこたち、
Hey, Choco...
もう二度と会えないの？
Are we never going to meet again?
不思議ね。キミの言葉を聞くと、なんだか元気が出てきちゃう。
It's strange. Listening to your words somehow fills me with energy.
もしかして、人間？
Are you... a human?
ねぇ、もしよければキミに、ちょこの思い出話、聞いてほしいの。
Hey, if you don't mind, I want you to listen to Choco's memories.
「The Beginning」プロジェクト始動！
"The Beginning" project starts!
はい！というわけで、ゆずチョコ、
Yes! So, Choco's...保存
12ヶ月連続オリ曲リリースが決定しました！
12-month consecutive original song release is decided!
はーい！しかもこちら
Yes! What's more, here...
なんとオリ曲に
...for our original songs...
ストーリー連動のボイスドラマが
...voice dramas linked to the stories...
一緒に、リリースされます！
...will be released together with them!
え、こちらね、約1話から12話まで
They will run from episode 1 to 12,
1曲ずつに連動して
with each song linking to one,
ボイスドラマもあるので、ぜひぜひ楽しみにしててくださーい！
so please look forward to the voice dramas too!
そして今回はね、その記念すべき
And today, to commemorate this...
1曲目を
...the very first song...
これから披露したいと思います！
...I will perform it now!
それでは聞いてください
Please listen to...
「キミの秒針」
..."Your Second Hand."
戻れないから また
Because we can't go back, once again...
愛しさが増す 君に
...my love deepens. I want to...
会いたいよ
...see you.
君から受け取った 壊れそうなストーリー
The fragile story I received from you...
どこまでも広がる 青い空
...stretches endlessly like the blue sky.
変わらない毎日も 色のない夢も
Even the unchanging days and colorless dreams...
手放して始めようよ
...let's let them go and start anew.
不安の夜を数え
Counting the nights of anxiety...
泣きながら迎えた 朝でもいい
...it's fine even if we greet the morning in tears.
時計の針のように
Like the hands of a clock...
刻んだ思い出たち 広げた
...we unfold the memories we carved.
戻れないから また
Because we can't go back, once again...
愛しさが増す 君に
...my love deepens. I want to...
会いたいよ
...see you.
二人で温めた 大切なストーリー
The precious story the two of us nurtured...
遠くまで続いた 果てない道
...was an endless road stretching far away.
「疲れたら代わるから」 そう言ってくれた
"I'll take over if you're tired," you told me.
優しさに触れて 見えた
Touching that kindness, I finally saw...
受け入れてくれたこと
...how much you had accepted me.
忘れない 嬉しくて満ちた日々
I won't forget those days filled with joy.
雨上がりの胸に
In my heart after the rain...
架かった虹のように 綺麗な
...like a beautiful rainbow that appeared...
君からの言葉
...the words from you...
一つ一つが 今も
...each and every one of them...
宝物
...is still a treasure.
支えてくれたから
Because you supported me...
輝ける この気持ち届けよう
...let me deliver this shining feeling to you.
時計の針のように
Like the hands of a clock...
刻んだ思い出たち 広げた
...we unfold the memories we carved.
戻れないから また
Because we can't go back, once again...
愛しさが増す 君に
...my love deepens. I want to...
会いたいよ
...see you.
雨上がりの胸に
In my heart after the rain...
架かった虹のように 綺麗な
...like a beautiful rainbow that appeared...
君からの言葉
...the words from you...
一つ一つが
...each and every one...
今も 宝物
...is still a treasure.
はい！ということで、みんなどうだったかな？
Yes! So, how did everyone like it?
今回の新曲「キミの秒針」は
My new song this time, "Kimi no Byoushin,"
しどの魔王様が作詞、
has lyrics written by Shidono Maou-sama,
そして、りめぐみあち様が作曲、編曲、
and music composed and arranged by Limegumi Achi-sama.
そして編曲にはなんと、加藤タカユキ様も加わっていただきました！
And for the arrangement, Katou Takayuki-sama also joined in!
いや、今回はボイスドラマ連動企画の第一弾として、
This song is the first part of a voice-drama-linked project,
ストーリー全体のテーマソングを担うような、劇的な楽曲に仕上がっております。
and it's crafted to be a dramatic piece serving as the main theme.
ドラマの鍵となるね、「秒針」というメタファーにも要注目してください！
Please pay close attention to the metaphor of the "second hand," which is key!
しどさんだけではなく、この後の豪華アーティストの皆様にもたくさん書いていただいたので、
Not only Shido-san, but many wonderful artists have contributed as well,
皆様リリースをお楽しみに！
so please look forward to the release!
こちらの「キミの秒針」は、各音楽サイトはちょっと間が空いちゃうんだけど、
For other music distribution sites, there will be a bit of a delay, but
3月15日の0時から配信予定でございます！
"Kimi no Byoushin" is scheduled for release at midnight on March 15th!
ま、ちょっとね公開まで時間があるから、それまでこの配信、何度も見返してみてください！
Since there's some time until the release, please rewatch this stream many times!
聴き込んでね！
Listen to it a lot, okay?
そしてそして、MVもね、ちょっと後日公開なので、楽しみにしててくださーい！
And the music video will be released at a later date, so stay tuned!
ということで、今日のチョコの生誕ライブはどうだったかな？
With that said, how was Choco's birthday live concert today?
ま、この後はすぐに、
Right after this,
ちょっとね、冒頭、最初の方でお披露目した、
we'll have the premiere of the MV we previewed at the start,
ノエちゃんとラミィちゃんとの3人の「初恋大戦争」のMV公開があって、
which is "Hatsukoi Daisensou" featuring Noel-chan and Lamy-chan!
そのあと！
And after that,
メン限で、ちょっとライブと、撮影会の続きとか、
we'll have a member-only after-live stream with a photoshoot,
ちょっとね、メン限でしか見れないシチュエーションドラマとかやるので、
and we'll do some situation dramas you can only see on the member-only stream!
ぜひぜひ気になる方は見に来てください！
If you're interested, please come and join us!
それでは、また後でお会いしましょう！
Well then, see you all again later!
お疲れーと！はむっ！
Otsukare-to! *munch*
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!